{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 9\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "23, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 9) \u003d 14, -(x - 9) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 16\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-14, -18", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 16) \u003d 2, -(x + 16) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 10\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "28, -8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 10) \u003d 18, -(x - 10) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 15\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-9, -21", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 15) \u003d 6, -(x + 15) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 7\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "25, -11", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 7) \u003d 18, -(x - 7) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 19\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-13, -25", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 19) \u003d 6, -(x + 19) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 8\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "10, 6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 8) \u003d 2, -(x - 8) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 18\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "-8, -28", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 18) \u003d 10, -(x + 18) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 5\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "7, 3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 5) \u003d 2, -(x - 5) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 21\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-19, -23", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 21) \u003d 2, -(x + 21) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 6\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "12, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 6) \u003d 6, -(x - 6) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 20\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "-6, -34", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 20) \u003d 14, -(x + 20) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 3\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "9, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 3) \u003d 6, -(x - 3) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 23\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-17, -29", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 23) \u003d 6, -(x + 23) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 4\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "14, -6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 4) \u003d 10, -(x - 4) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 22\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "-4, -40", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 22) \u003d 18, -(x + 22) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 18\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "36, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 18) \u003d 18, -(x - 18) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 8\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-2, -14", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 8) \u003d 6, -(x + 8) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 19\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "29, 9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 19) \u003d 10, -(x - 19) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 7\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "3, -17", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 7) \u003d 10, -(x + 7) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 16\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "18, 14", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 16) \u003d 2, -(x - 16) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 10\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "0, -20", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 10) \u003d 10, -(x + 10) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 17\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "31, 3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 17) \u003d 14, -(x - 17) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 9\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "5, -23", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 9) \u003d 14, -(x + 9) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 14\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "20, 8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 14) \u003d 6, -(x - 14) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 12\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "2, -26", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 12) \u003d 14, -(x + 12) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 15\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "33, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 15) \u003d 18, -(x - 15) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 11\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "7, -29", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 11) \u003d 18, -(x + 11) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 11\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "21, 1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 11) \u003d 10, -(x - 11) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 14\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "4, -32", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 14) \u003d 18, -(x + 14) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 12\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "14, 10", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 12) \u003d 2, -(x - 12) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 13\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-11, -15", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 13) \u003d 2, -(x + 13) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 18\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-12, -24", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 18) \u003d 6, -(x + 18) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 7\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "21, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 7) \u003d 14, -(x - 7) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 17\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "1, -35", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 17) \u003d 18, -(x + 17) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 8\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "26, -10", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 8) \u003d 18, -(x - 8) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 20\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "-10, -30", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 20) \u003d 10, -(x + 20) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 5\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "23, -13", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 5) \u003d 18, -(x - 5) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 19\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-17, -21", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 19) \u003d 2, -(x + 19) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 6\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "8, 4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 6) \u003d 2, -(x - 6) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 22\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "-8, -36", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 22) \u003d 14, -(x + 22) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 2\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "4, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 2) \u003d 2, -(x - 2) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 21\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-15, -27", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 21) \u003d 6, -(x + 21) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 3\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "9, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 3) \u003d 6, -(x - 3) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 24\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "-6, -42", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 24) \u003d 18, -(x + 24) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x) \u003d 6, -(x) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 23\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-21, -25", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 23) \u003d 2, -(x + 23) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 1\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "11, -9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 1) \u003d 10, -(x - 1) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 9\\right| \u003d 11", "answer": "2, -20", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 9) \u003d 11, -(x + 9) \u003d 11\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 16\\right| \u003d 19", "answer": "35, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 16) \u003d 19, -(x - 16) \u003d 19\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 8\\right| \u003d 3", "answer": "-5, -11", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 8) \u003d 3, -(x + 8) \u003d 3\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 17\\right| \u003d 11", "answer": "28, 6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 17) \u003d 11, -(x - 17) \u003d 11\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 11\\right| \u003d 15", "answer": "4, -26", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 11) \u003d 15, -(x + 11) \u003d 15\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 13\\right| \u003d 3", "answer": "16, 10", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 13) \u003d 3, -(x - 13) \u003d 3\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 10\\right| \u003d 7", "answer": "-3, -17", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 10) \u003d 7, -(x + 10) \u003d 7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 14\\right| \u003d 15", "answer": "29, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 14) \u003d 15, -(x - 14) \u003d 15\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 13\\right| \u003d 19", "answer": "6, -32", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 13) \u003d 19, -(x + 13) \u003d 19\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 11\\right| \u003d 7", "answer": "18, 4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 11) \u003d 7, -(x - 11) \u003d 7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 12\\right| \u003d 11", "answer": "-1, -23", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 12) \u003d 11, -(x + 12) \u003d 11\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 12\\right| \u003d 19", "answer": "31, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 12) \u003d 19, -(x - 12) \u003d 19\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 15\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-13, -17", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 15) \u003d 2, -(x + 15) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 9\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "19, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 9) \u003d 10, -(x - 9) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 14\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "0, -28", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 14) \u003d 14, -(x + 14) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 10\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "12, 8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 10) \u003d 2, -(x - 10) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 15\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "33, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 15) \u003d 18, -(x - 15) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 11\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "7, -29", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 11) \u003d 18, -(x + 11) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 16\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "18, 14", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 16) \u003d 2, -(x - 16) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 10\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "0, -20", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 10) \u003d 10, -(x + 10) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 13\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "27, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 13) \u003d 14, -(x - 13) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 13\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-11, -15", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 13) \u003d 2, -(x + 13) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 14\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "20, 8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 14) \u003d 6, -(x - 14) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 12\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "2, -26", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 12) \u003d 14, -(x + 12) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 10\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "28, -8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 10) \u003d 18, -(x - 10) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 15\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-9, -21", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 15) \u003d 6, -(x + 15) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 11\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "21, 1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 11) \u003d 10, -(x - 11) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 14\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "4, -32", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 14) \u003d 18, -(x + 14) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 8\\right| \u003d 1", "answer": "9, 7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 8) \u003d 1, -(x - 8) \u003d 1\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 17\\right| \u003d 9", "answer": "-8, -26", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 17) \u003d 9, -(x + 17) \u003d 9\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 9\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "23, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 9) \u003d 14, -(x - 9) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 16\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-14, -18", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 16) \u003d 2, -(x + 16) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 26\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-24, -28", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 26) \u003d 2, -(x + 26) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 2\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "8, -12", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 2) \u003d 10, -(x + 2) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 25\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-19, -31", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 25) \u003d 6, -(x + 25) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 1\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "13, -15", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 1) \u003d 14, -(x + 1) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 29\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-23, -35", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 29) \u003d 6, -(x + 29) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 4\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "10, -18", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 4) \u003d 14, -(x + 4) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 28\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "-18, -38", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 28) \u003d 10, -(x + 28) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 3\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "15, -21", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 3) \u003d 18, -(x + 3) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 19\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "29, 9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 19) \u003d 10, -(x - 19) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 6\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "4, -16", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 6) \u003d 10, -(x + 6) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 20\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "34, 6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 20) \u003d 14, -(x - 20) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 5\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "-3, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 5) \u003d 2, -(x + 5) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 17\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "31, 3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 17) \u003d 14, -(x - 17) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 9\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "5, -23", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 9) \u003d 14, -(x + 9) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 18\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "36, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 18) \u003d 18, -(x - 18) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 8\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "-2, -14", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 8) \u003d 6, -(x + 8) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 3\\right| \u003d 1", "answer": "-2, -4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 3) \u003d 1, -(x + 3) \u003d 1\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 28\\right| \u003d 9", "answer": "-19, -37", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 28) \u003d 9, -(x + 28) \u003d 9\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 2\\right| \u003d 13", "answer": "11, -15", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 2) \u003d 13, -(x + 2) \u003d 13\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 27\\right| \u003d 13", "answer": "-14, -40", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 27) \u003d 13, -(x + 27) \u003d 13\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 10\\right| \u003d -3", "answer": "7, 13", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 10) \u003d -3, -(x - 10) \u003d -3\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|3x - 18\\right| \u003d 9", "answer": "9, 3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(3x - 18) \u003d 9, -(3x - 18) \u003d 9\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 1\\right| \u003d -4", "answer": "-3, 5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 1) \u003d -4, -(x - 1) \u003d -4\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x + 7\\right| \u003d -2", "answer": "-9, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x + 7) \u003d -2, -(x + 7) \u003d -2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|6x - 42\\right| \u003d -12", "answer": "5, 9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(6x - 42) \u003d -12, -(6x - 42) \u003d -12\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|6x - 24\\right| \u003d -18", "answer": "1, 7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(6x - 24) \u003d -18, -(6x - 24) \u003d -18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|3x + 3\\right| \u003d 15", "answer": "4, -6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(3x + 3) \u003d 15, -(3x + 3) \u003d 15\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|3x + 27\\right| \u003d 21", "answer": "-2, -16", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(3x + 27) \u003d 21, -(3x + 27) \u003d 21\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 5\\right| \u003d 7", "answer": "12, -2", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 5) \u003d 7, -(x - 5) \u003d 7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|x - 2\\right| \u003d 6", "answer": "8, -4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(x - 2) \u003d 6, -(x - 2) \u003d 6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|6x + 24\\right| \u003d -6", "answer": "-5, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(6x + 24) \u003d -6, -(6x + 24) \u003d -6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 56\\right| \u003d -7", "answer": "-9, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 56) \u003d -7, -(7x + 56) \u003d -7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 30\\right| \u003d 35", "answer": "13, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 30) \u003d 35, -(5x - 30) \u003d 35\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 21\\right| \u003d -14", "answer": "1, 5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 21) \u003d -14, -(7x - 21) \u003d -14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x + 12\\right| \u003d 24", "answer": "3, -9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x + 12) \u003d 24, -(4x + 12) \u003d 24\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x - 40\\right| \u003d 32", "answer": "18, 2", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x - 40) \u003d 32, -(4x - 40) \u003d 32\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 8\\right| \u003d 2", "answer": "5, 3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 8) \u003d 2, -(2x - 8) \u003d 2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 2\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "8, -6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 2) \u003d 14, -(2x - 2) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 35\\right| \u003d 0", "answer": "-5, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 35) \u003d 0, -(7x + 35) \u003d 0\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 49\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "9, 5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 49) \u003d 14, -(7x - 49) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x - 8\\right| \u003d 8", "answer": "4, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x - 8) \u003d 8, -(4x - 8) \u003d 8\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 10\\right| \u003d 5", "answer": "-1, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 10) \u003d 5, -(5x + 10) \u003d 5\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 14\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "2, -16", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 14) \u003d 18, -(2x + 14) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 10\\right| \u003d -10", "answer": "0, 10", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 10) \u003d -10, -(2x - 10) \u003d -10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x\\right| \u003d -35", "answer": "-5, 5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x) \u003d -35, -(7x) \u003d -35\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 8\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "5, -13", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 8) \u003d 18, -(2x + 8) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 63\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "-7, -11", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 63) \u003d 14, -(7x + 63) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 2\\right| \u003d 16", "answer": "9, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 2) \u003d 16, -(2x - 2) \u003d 16\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 35\\right| \u003d 7", "answer": "-4, -6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 35) \u003d 7, -(7x + 35) \u003d 7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 56\\right| \u003d 0", "answer": "-8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 56) \u003d 0, -(7x + 56) \u003d 0\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x - 24\\right| \u003d 0", "answer": "6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x - 24) \u003d 0, -(4x - 24) \u003d 0\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 10\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "0, -4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 10) \u003d 10, -(5x + 10) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 14\\right| \u003d -10", "answer": "-12, -2", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 14) \u003d -10, -(2x + 14) \u003d -10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x - 36\\right| \u003d 36", "answer": "18, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x - 36) \u003d 36, -(4x - 36) \u003d 36\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 8\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "13, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 8) \u003d 18, -(2x - 8) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 8\\right| \u003d -8", "answer": "-8, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 8) \u003d -8, -(2x + 8) \u003d -8\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 63\\right| \u003d 28", "answer": "-5, -13", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 63) \u003d 28, -(7x + 63) \u003d 28\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 49\\right| \u003d 21", "answer": "10, 4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 49) \u003d 21, -(7x - 49) \u003d 21\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x - 8\\right| \u003d 12", "answer": "5, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x - 8) \u003d 12, -(4x - 8) \u003d 12\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x + 24\\right| \u003d 20", "answer": "-1, -11", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x + 24) \u003d 20, -(4x + 24) \u003d 20\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 16\\right| \u003d -4", "answer": "6, 10", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 16) \u003d -4, -(2x - 16) \u003d -4\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 10\\right| \u003d 8", "answer": "9, 1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 10) \u003d 8, -(2x - 10) \u003d 8\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x\\right| \u003d -21", "answer": "-3, 3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x) \u003d -21, -(7x) \u003d -21\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 30\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "-4, -8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 30) \u003d 10, -(5x + 30) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 18\\right| \u003d -10", "answer": "4, 14", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 18) \u003d -10, -(2x - 18) \u003d -10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 10\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "14, -4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 10) \u003d 18, -(2x - 10) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x) \u003d 14, -(7x) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 56\\right| \u003d -28", "answer": "-12, -4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 56) \u003d -28, -(7x + 56) \u003d -28\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 30\\right| \u003d 20", "answer": "10, 2", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 30) \u003d 20, -(5x - 30) \u003d 20\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 21\\right| \u003d 21", "answer": "6, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 21) \u003d 21, -(7x - 21) \u003d 21\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x + 8\\right| \u003d 12", "answer": "1, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x + 8) \u003d 12, -(4x + 8) \u003d 12\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 50\\right| \u003d 25", "answer": "15, 5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 50) \u003d 25, -(5x - 50) \u003d 25\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 28\\right| \u003d -14", "answer": "2, 6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 28) \u003d -14, -(7x - 28) \u003d -14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 2\\right| \u003d -6", "answer": "-2, 4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 2) \u003d -6, -(2x - 2) \u003d -6\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 35\\right| \u003d -21", "answer": "-8, -2", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 35) \u003d -21, -(7x + 35) \u003d -21\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 56\\right| \u003d -7", "answer": "7, 9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 56) \u003d -7, -(7x - 56) \u003d -7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 10\\right| \u003d 35", "answer": "9, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 10) \u003d 35, -(5x - 10) \u003d 35\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 5\\right| \u003d 30", "answer": "5, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 5) \u003d 30, -(5x + 5) \u003d 30\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 14\\right| \u003d 12", "answer": "-1, -13", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 14) \u003d 12, -(2x + 14) \u003d 12\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 21\\right| \u003d 28", "answer": "7, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 21) \u003d 28, -(7x - 21) \u003d 28\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x + 12\\right| \u003d 16", "answer": "1, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x + 12) \u003d 16, -(4x + 12) \u003d 16\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 30\\right| \u003d 15", "answer": "-3, -9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 30) \u003d 15, -(5x + 30) \u003d 15\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 18\\right| \u003d -8", "answer": "5, 13", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 18) \u003d -8, -(2x - 18) \u003d -8\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 2\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "6, -4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 2) \u003d 10, -(2x - 2) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 35\\right| \u003d -14", "answer": "-7, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 35) \u003d -14, -(7x + 35) \u003d -14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 56\\right| \u003d -21", "answer": "-11, -5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 56) \u003d -21, -(7x + 56) \u003d -21\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 30\\right| \u003d 25", "answer": "11, 1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 30) \u003d 25, -(5x - 30) \u003d 25\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 5\\right| \u003d -5", "answer": "-2, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 5) \u003d -5, -(5x + 5) \u003d -5\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 14\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "0, -14", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 14) \u003d 14, -(2x + 14) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|4x - 40\\right| \u003d 24", "answer": "16, 4", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(4x - 40) \u003d 24, -(4x - 40) \u003d 24\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 8\\right| \u003d -2", "answer": "3, 5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 8) \u003d -2, -(2x - 8) \u003d -2\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 8\\right| \u003d 16", "answer": "4, -12", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 8) \u003d 16, -(2x + 8) \u003d 16\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 63\\right| \u003d 7", "answer": "-8, -10", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 63) \u003d 7, -(7x + 63) \u003d 7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 49\\right| \u003d 0", "answer": "7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 49) \u003d 0, -(7x - 49) \u003d 0\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 10\\right| \u003d 40", "answer": "10, -6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 10) \u003d 40, -(5x - 10) \u003d 40\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 6\\right| \u003d -4", "answer": "-5, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 6) \u003d -4, -(2x + 6) \u003d -4\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 45\\right| \u003d -10", "answer": "-11, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 45) \u003d -10, -(5x + 45) \u003d -10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 56\\right| \u003d -21", "answer": "5, 11", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 56) \u003d -21, -(7x - 56) \u003d -21\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 10\\right| \u003d 25", "answer": "7, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 10) \u003d 25, -(5x - 10) \u003d 25\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 30\\right| \u003d 35", "answer": "1, -13", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 30) \u003d 35, -(5x + 30) \u003d 35\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 18\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "16, 2", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 18) \u003d 14, -(2x - 18) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|3x - 15\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "11, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(3x - 15) \u003d 18, -(3x - 15) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x\\right| \u003d -7", "answer": "-1, 1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x) \u003d -7, -(7x) \u003d -7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 56\\right| \u003d 56", "answer": "0, -16", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 56) \u003d 56, -(7x + 56) \u003d 56\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 35\\right| \u003d 5", "answer": "8, 6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 35) \u003d 5, -(5x - 35) \u003d 5\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 21\\right| \u003d 0", "answer": "3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 21) \u003d 0, -(7x - 21) \u003d 0\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|3x + 6\\right| \u003d 24", "answer": "6, -10", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(3x + 6) \u003d 24, -(3x + 6) \u003d 24\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x - 50\\right| \u003d 10", "answer": "12, 8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x - 50) \u003d 10, -(5x - 50) \u003d 10\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 28\\right| \u003d -35", "answer": "-1, 9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 28) \u003d -35, -(7x - 28) \u003d -35\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 2\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "10, -8", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 2) \u003d 18, -(2x - 2) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x + 28\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "-2, -6", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x + 28) \u003d 14, -(7x + 28) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 10\\right| \u003d 16", "answer": "13, -3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 10) \u003d 16, -(2x - 10) \u003d 16\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x\\right| \u003d 7", "answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x) \u003d 7, -(7x) \u003d 7\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x + 8\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "3, -11", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x + 8) \u003d 14, -(2x + 8) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 45\\right| \u003d 0", "answer": "-9", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 45) \u003d 0, -(5x + 45) \u003d 0\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|7x - 21\\right| \u003d 14", "answer": "5, 1", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(7x - 21) \u003d 14, -(7x - 21) \u003d 14\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|3x + 6\\right| \u003d -15", "answer": "-7, 3", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(3x + 6) \u003d -15, -(3x + 6) \u003d -15\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|5x + 30\\right| \u003d 5", "answer": "-5, -7", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(5x + 30) \u003d 5, -(5x + 30) \u003d 5\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 18\\right| \u003d 18", "answer": "18, 0", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 18) \u003d 18, -(2x - 18) \u003d 18\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "\\(\\left|2x - 2\\right| \u003d -8", "answer": "-3, 5", "explanation": "The function inside the absolute can be both positive and negative\n(2x - 2) \u003d -8, -(2x - 2) \u003d -8\nSolve both equations for x", "prompt": "x \u003d"}
]}